# **Thomaz**

#### **MS** Researcher

## Thomaz Guadagnini Ramalheira

Campinas, SP - Brazil

github.com/ThomazGR thomaz@vivaldi.net thomazgr.github.io

#### Skills

Former Undergraduate Researcher with over two years of experience in running analysis, tests and experimental work in a scientific research laboratory environment. Nowadays I am pursuing my Masters degree in Nutritional Sciences and Metabolism at UNICAMP. Skills include good connection between development and biological data, problem solving and good communication.

## Professional experience

#### MSc in Nutritional Sciences and Metabolism | UNICAMP

FEBRUARY 2020 - PRESENT, LIMEIRA

Working with development and utilization of Bioinformatics tools based on biological data analysis.

-Python:

-SciPy, Pandas, Statsmodels, Numpy, GEOParse.

- -Excel/Google Sheets;
- -Statistical analysis and data visualization;
- -SQL;
- -Making reports;
- -Bioinformatics tools:

-KEGG, Gene Ontology, Cytoscape, GEO/GEO2R, etc.

#### Undergraduate Researcher | UNICAMP

JULY 2017 - JULY 2019, LIMEIRA

- -Statistical analysis utilizing GraphPad Prism;
- -Making reports.

### **Education**

## BSc in Sport Sciences | UNICAMP

JANUARY 2015 - JULY 2019, LIMEIRA

Undergraduate thesis: Influence of acute physical exercise in hepatic and muscular expression of microRNAs in offspring of mice with diet-induced obesity.

### Languages

#### **English**

Level: Advanced